{
    "data_info": {
        "documentID": "J_FOOD_089668",
        "source": "도서",
        "writer": "스타일북스 편집부",
        "ISBN_ISNN": "978-89-6260-384-2",
        "version": "초판",
        "source_language": "ko",
        "translator": "파파고",
        "source_url": "커피 앳 카페",
        "collectedDate": "2023-11-03",
        "publishedDate": "2012-05-25",
        "domain": "음식점",
        "title": "엘 라고"
    },
    "text": "エラゴヨーグルト、6,500ウォン、エラゴアイスラテ、6,500ウォン、アメリカーノ,4,500ウォン、カフェラテ、5,000ウォン、バニララテ,5,500ウォン、カフェモカ 、5,500ウォン、キャラメルマキアート 、5,500ウォン、エスプレッソ 、4,500ウォン 、アフォガート 、5,500ウォン 、バニラシロップラテ 、6,000ウォン 、抹茶ラテ/チョコラテ、5,000ウォン, プレーンヨーグルトスムージー、6,000ウォン、イチゴヨーグルトスムージー、6,000ウォンです。",
    "QA": [
        {
            "question": "エラゴヨーグルトの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "6,500ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "エラゴアイスラテの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "6,500ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "アメリカーノの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "4,500ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "カフェラテの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "5,000ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "バニララテの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "5,500ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "カフェモカの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "5,500ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "キャラメルマキアートの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "5,500ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "エスプレッソの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "4,500ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "アフォガートの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "5,500ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "バニラシロップラテの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "6,000ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "抹茶ラテ/チョコラテの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "5,000ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "プレーンヨーグルトスムージーの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "6,000ウォンです。"
        },
        {
            "question": "イチゴヨーグルトスムージーの値段はいくらですか？",
            "answer": "6,000ウォンです。"
        }
    ],
    "word_Count": {
        "text": 180,
        "QA": 286
    }
}